[{"id":0,"question":"9*7","choices":[62,63,64],"rightAnswer":63,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":1,"question":"7*5","choices":[34,35,36],"rightAnswer":35,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"question":"1*7","choices":[6,7,8],"rightAnswer":7,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"question":"8*8","choices":[63,64,65],"rightAnswer":64,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"question":"7*4","choices":[27,28,29],"rightAnswer":28,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":5,"question":"5*6","choices":[29,30,31],"rightAnswer":30,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":6,"question":"7*4","choices":[27,28,29],"rightAnswer":28,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":7,"question":"7*7","choices":[48,49,50],"rightAnswer":49,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":8,"question":"6*2","choices":[11,12,13],"rightAnswer":12,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":9,"question":"7*6","choices":[41,42,43],"rightAnswer":42,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":10,"question":"7*8","choices":[55,56,57],"rightAnswer":56,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":11,"question":"5*8","choices":[39,40,41],"rightAnswer":40,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":12,"question":"1*1","choices":[0,1,2],"rightAnswer":1,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":13,"question":"8*1","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":14,"question":"1*8","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":15,"question":"8*3","choices":[23,24,25],"rightAnswer":24,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":16,"question":"7*1","choices":[6,7,8],"rightAnswer":7,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":17,"question":"5*9","choices":[44,45,46],"rightAnswer":45,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":18,"question":"6*6","choices":[35,36,37],"rightAnswer":36,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":19,"question":"2*8","choices":[15,16,17],"rightAnswer":16,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":20,"question":"30*4","choices":[119,120,121],"rightAnswer":120,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":21,"question":"62*5","choices":[309,310,311],"rightAnswer":310,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":22,"question":"88*5","choices":[439,440,441],"rightAnswer":440,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":23,"question":"99*3","choices":[296,297,298],"rightAnswer":297,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":24,"question":"19*8","choices":[151,152,153],"rightAnswer":152,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":25,"question":"56*9","choices":[503,504,505],"rightAnswer":504,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":26,"question":"24*1","choices":[23,24,25],"rightAnswer":24,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":27,"question":"56*2","choices":[111,112,113],"rightAnswer":112,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":28,"question":"89*1","choices":[88,89,90],"rightAnswer":89,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":29,"question":"84*3","choices":[251,252,253],"rightAnswer":252,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":30,"question":"69*8","choices":[551,552,553],"rightAnswer":552,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":31,"question":"92*8","choices":[735,736,737],"rightAnswer":736,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":32,"question":"62*1","choices":[61,62,63],"rightAnswer":62,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":33,"question":"30*2","choices":[59,60,61],"rightAnswer":60,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":34,"question":"73*2","choices":[145,146,147],"rightAnswer":146,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":35,"question":"36*6","choices":[215,216,217],"rightAnswer":216,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":36,"question":"23*4","choices":[91,92,93],"rightAnswer":92,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":37,"question":"93*2","choices":[185,186,187],"rightAnswer":186,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":38,"question":"89*6","choices":[533,534,535],"rightAnswer":534,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":39,"question":"23*3","choices":[68,69,70],"rightAnswer":69,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":40,"question":"26*74","choices":[1923,1924,1925],"rightAnswer":1924,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":41,"question":"95*49","choices":[4654,4655,4656],"rightAnswer":4655,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":42,"question":"74*51","choices":[3773,3774,3775],"rightAnswer":3774,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":43,"question":"36*70","choices":[2519,2520,2521],"rightAnswer":2520,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":44,"question":"54*79","choices":[4265,4266,4267],"rightAnswer":4266,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":45,"question":"55*24","choices":[1319,1320,1321],"rightAnswer":1320,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":46,"question":"14*88","choices":[1231,1232,1233],"rightAnswer":1232,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":47,"question":"22*88","choices":[1935,1936,1937],"rightAnswer":1936,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":48,"question":"91*93","choices":[8462,8463,8464],"rightAnswer":8463,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":49,"question":"45*76","choices":[3419,3420,3421],"rightAnswer":3420,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":50,"question":"12*33","choices":[395,396,397],"rightAnswer":396,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":51,"question":"37*87","choices":[3218,3219,3220],"rightAnswer":3219,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":52,"question":"64*51","choices":[3263,3264,3265],"rightAnswer":3264,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":53,"question":"80*61","choices":[4879,4880,4881],"rightAnswer":4880,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":54,"question":"27*93","choices":[2510,2511,2512],"rightAnswer":2511,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":55,"question":"58*24","choices":[1391,1392,1393],"rightAnswer":1392,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":56,"question":"88*62","choices":[5455,5456,5457],"rightAnswer":5456,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":57,"question":"42*57","choices":[2393,2394,2395],"rightAnswer":2394,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":58,"question":"97*40","choices":[3879,3880,3881],"rightAnswer":3880,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":59,"question":"44*77","choices":[3387,3388,3389],"rightAnswer":3388,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":60,"question":"978*46","choices":[44987,44988,44989],"rightAnswer":44988,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":61,"question":"495*96","choices":[47519,47520,47521],"rightAnswer":47520,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":62,"question":"610*70","choices":[42699,42700,42701],"rightAnswer":42700,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":63,"question":"661*46","choices":[30405,30406,30407],"rightAnswer":30406,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":64,"question":"657*64","choices":[42047,42048,42049],"rightAnswer":42048,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":65,"question":"674*51","choices":[34373,34374,34375],"rightAnswer":34374,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":66,"question":"195*91","choices":[17744,17745,17746],"rightAnswer":17745,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":67,"question":"781*58","choices":[45297,45298,45299],"rightAnswer":45298,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":68,"question":"983*40","choices":[39319,39320,39321],"rightAnswer":39320,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":69,"question":"600*70","choices":[41999,42000,42001],"rightAnswer":42000,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":70,"question":"687*39","choices":[26792,26793,26794],"rightAnswer":26793,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":71,"question":"729*79","choices":[57590,57591,57592],"rightAnswer":57591,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":72,"question":"907*41","choices":[37186,37187,37188],"rightAnswer":37187,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":73,"question":"544*62","choices":[33727,33728,33729],"rightAnswer":33728,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":74,"question":"468*99","choices":[46331,46332,46333],"rightAnswer":46332,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":75,"question":"693*55","choices":[38114,38115,38116],"rightAnswer":38115,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":76,"question":"621*10","choices":[6209,6210,6211],"rightAnswer":6210,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":77,"question":"163*46","choices":[7497,7498,7499],"rightAnswer":7498,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":78,"question":"370*18","choices":[6659,6660,6661],"rightAnswer":6660,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":79,"question":"460*69","choices":[31739,31740,31741],"rightAnswer":31740,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":80,"question":"571*974","choices":[556153,556154,556155],"rightAnswer":556154,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":81,"question":"472*886","choices":[418191,418192,418193],"rightAnswer":418192,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":82,"question":"608*308","choices":[187263,187264,187265],"rightAnswer":187264,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":83,"question":"849*520","choices":[441479,441480,441481],"rightAnswer":441480,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":84,"question":"666*204","choices":[135863,135864,135865],"rightAnswer":135864,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":85,"question":"305*186","choices":[56729,56730,56731],"rightAnswer":56730,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":86,"question":"150*842","choices":[126299,126300,126301],"rightAnswer":126300,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":87,"question":"946*241","choices":[227985,227986,227987],"rightAnswer":227986,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":88,"question":"645*556","choices":[358619,358620,358621],"rightAnswer":358620,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":89,"question":"257*944","choices":[242607,242608,242609],"rightAnswer":242608,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":90,"question":"148*216","choices":[31967,31968,31969],"rightAnswer":31968,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":91,"question":"857*480","choices":[411359,411360,411361],"rightAnswer":411360,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":92,"question":"516*369","choices":[190403,190404,190405],"rightAnswer":190404,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":93,"question":"173*438","choices":[75773,75774,75775],"rightAnswer":75774,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":94,"question":"954*197","choices":[187937,187938,187939],"rightAnswer":187938,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":95,"question":"227*758","choices":[172065,172066,172067],"rightAnswer":172066,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":96,"question":"229*376","choices":[86103,86104,86105],"rightAnswer":86104,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":97,"question":"363*647","choices":[234860,234861,234862],"rightAnswer":234861,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":98,"question":"788*339","choices":[267131,267132,267133],"rightAnswer":267132,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":99,"question":"236*794","choices":[187383,187384,187385],"rightAnswer":187384,"qOperator":"*","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false}]